<sburb description="giftshop">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="giftshopBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/giftshop.png</asset>
    <asset name="giftshopMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/giftshopcoll.png</asset>
    <asset name="mal" type="graphic">objects/npcs/malsprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="dersite1" type="graphic">objects/npcs/dersite1sprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="prospitan3" type="graphic">objects/npcs/prospitan3sprite.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='giftshop' walkableMap='giftshopMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='giftshopBG'>
	    <animation sheet='giftshopBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,400,555,457,500</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/shop.xml,shop,1012,910</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	</triggers>

	<sprite name='malPlace' x='432' y='380' width='122' height='104' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='mal' x='-60' y='-50'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to Gift Shop Clerk.'>
		<args>
			@mal_talk ???: Welcome to Mal’s gift emporium your one stop shop for all your tourism needs
@mal_talk Mal: we got anything you could want. at least 2 guns, attunements, fraymotiffs, and  snowglobes with trees in em.
@vrachne_confused Vrachne: what the hell is an “attunement?”
@mal_shrug Mal: hell if i know i’m just sellin them.
@mal_peeved Mal: just found em in a fancy box in a lake, so they’re locally sourced 
@mal_peeved Mal: and anyone with a business degree knows that anything locally sourced is usually pretty good.
@mal_peeved Mal: i don’t know about you but i wouldn’t wanna stick any needles in me if i didn’t know where they came from
@mal_peeved Mal: but these attunement needles are top of the line locally sourced yes mam
@vrachne_smug Vrachne: lake needles huh? really a big ticket item, i’m sure they’ll fly off the shelves
@mal_peeved Mal: are you fuzzing about what i’m selling in my shop?
@mal_peeved Mal: where’s your business degree “missy” huh?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: wel-
@mal_peeved Mal: oh wait don’t tell me i can already tell where it is.
@mal_peeved Mal: it’s up your ass!
@mal_peeved Mal: if you aren’t buying anything then fuck off.
@mal_peeved Mal: you and your buddies malformed head arms are scaring off paying customers
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i’m sure that attitude will catch up with you.
@mal_peeved Mal: mhm whatever you say.  ghzbe purfg.
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	
	<sprite name='dersite1Place' x='537' y='297' width='22' height='96' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='dersite1' x='-10' y='-20'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to Dersite.'>
		<args>
			@! I’ve always wanted one of these old timey diving suits, but she’s asking for a whole #f360f4 BOONCASE! ## What a ripoff.

			With that kinda moolah you could make your own diving suit, give it some cool mechanical parts and stuff too! 

			Maybe that’s what I’ll do with my leftover war bonds; I’ve come to find out that traveling around like this really ain’t my sorta thing.
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='prospitan3Place' x='810' y='436' width='22' height='62' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='prospitan3' x='-10' y='-20'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to Prospitan.'>
		<args>
			@! Man, the lady who runs this place is a scam artist! I blew a whole #f360f4 BOONBUCK ## on a “mystery box” and all I got was this lousy T-shirt and some “attunements”, and I don’t even know what the hell an “attunement” is!

The lady running the shop says they’re just some sort of medical thing, but what kind of medicine is called “#6aa84f Blooming## #a64d79 Love## #9fc5e8 White##“ or “#f6b26b Lightworkers## #f9cb9c Blessings##“. Maybe it’s herbal or something? I don’t know.

Ugh, I feel like I just took part in a back alley drug deal or something. This’ll be the last time I ever spend money at a gift shop, that’s for sure.
			
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>