<sburb description="shop">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="shopBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map3.png</asset>
    <asset name="shopMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/map3coll.png</asset>
    <asset name="shopFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map3_fg.png</asset>
    <asset name="log" type="graphic">objects/npcs/logsprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="dersite1" type="graphic">objects/npcs/dersite1sprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="child" type="graphic">objects/npcs/childsprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="female" type="graphic">objects/npcs/femalesprite.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='shop' walkableMap='shopMap' mapScale="1">
	<sprite name="shopFG" depthing="2">
        <animation sheet="shopFG" />
      </sprite>
	  <sprite name='shopBG'>
	    <animation sheet='shopBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
		<trigger>
  			<args>inBox2,char,2370,1130,2410,870</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/square.xml,square,150,900</args>
			</action>
  		</trigger>
		<trigger>
			<args>inBox2,char,985,837,1043,786</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/giftshop.xml,giftshop,431,475</args>
			</action>
		</trigger>
		<trigger detonate='true'>
		<args>spriteProperty,char,x &lt; 900</args>
		<action command='talk'>
		<args>
@vrachne_surprised Vrachne: god do these roads ever end?!
@vrachne_surprised Vrachne: i’m getting tired of floating around this place.
@dickle_happy Dickle: VRACHNE WAIT!!
@dickle_happy Dickle: there’s a crack!
@vrachne_confused Vrachne: what about it?
@dickle_excited Dickle: those things aren’t good to go over ya know!
@dickle_excited Dickle: there’s a saying about it and everything!
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: mhm yeah. sure there is.
@dickle_talk Dickle: i’m not joking, i’m being completely serious, honest!
@vrachne_smug Vrachne: what’s the saying then huh?
@dickle_talk Dickle: alright it goes something like uh.
@dickle_talk Dickle: Wenn du auf einem Riss gehst, brichst du deiner Mutter den Rücken!
@dickle_talk Dickle: to put that into like english that’s uh “if you walk on a crack you break your mama’s back!” or something along those lines
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: I FLOAT.
@dickle_talk Dickle: that’s even worse! Because there’s a totally different saying for that exact sorta thing!
@dickle_talk Dickle: Wenn Sie über einem Riss schweben, Sie brechen sich den Rücken!
@dickle_talk Dickle: “When you hover over a crack, you break your own back!”
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: I DONT HAVE BONES.
@dickle_talk Dickle: still is that something you really wanna risk?!
@dickle_talk Dickle: those kinda haunted sayings have a way of catching up with you, trust me i’d know! And don’t ask me how i know because i really rather not go into it!
@dickle_talk Dickle: plus i’m sure we’ll get totally lost if we wander off too far so let’s just stay here okay?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: you didn’t have to go into that entire spiel about cracks if that’s all you wanted to tell me.
@dickle_talk Dickle: yeah but that’s way less fun hehe
@dickle_talk Dickle: plus i bet you would get on my case too if i started wandering too far off, so it’s only fair!
@dickle_talk Vrachne: i woul-
@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: honestly you know what? forget it. I don’t care anymore, this place sucks anyway let’s just go back.
@dickle_excited Dickle: fine by me! there’s still plenty of stuff to explore in this part of town anyway!
	</args>
	</action>
	</trigger>
	</triggers>
	<sprite name='child' x='1340' y='775' width='30' height='48' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='child' x='-10' y='-10'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
			@! Znzn gbyq zr vs v ybbx guebhtu genfu pnaf naq fryy gur vagrerfgvat fghss v pna or fhpprffshy whfg yvxr zf zny-zny!
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='female' x='930' y='865' width='30' height='48' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='female' x='-20' y='-30'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
			@! V jbhyqa'g ohl nalguvat urer, Zny'f n gbgny purncfxngr, nyy fur fryyf vf yvgreny genfu.

Fur hfrq gb gel naq cnja gur fghss fur tbg ba ure qrrc qvirf gb gur erfg bs gur crbcyr va gbja, gunaxshyyl abobql obhtug vagb ure penc, yrnfg gvyy gur gbhevfgf pnzr nebhaq.

Vs vg jnfa'g sbe gurz fur'q cebonoyl ybfr gur ohvyqvat, V'q ybir gb frr gur ybbx ba ure snpr vs gung unccrarq.

		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='dersite1' x='1430' y='785' width='25' height='40' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='dersite1' x='-20' y='-25'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to Dersite.'>
		<args>
			@! I wanted #0b5394 ICE ##but all they have here is #0b5394 VPR ##, which happens to look suspiciously close to #0b5394 ICE##!

I don’t know what’s going on here, but I wouldn’t go sticking whatever this stuff is into your drinks, it’s probably not safe!
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='log' x='1742' y='867' width='30' height='48' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='log' x='-20' y='-25'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
			@vrachne_concerned Vrachne: Damn. You hate to see it.
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>