<sburb description="sisshop">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="sisshopBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/sisshop.png</asset>
    <asset name="sisshopMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/sisshopcoll.png</asset>
    <asset name="sisshopFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/sisshop_fg.png</asset>
    <asset name="allay" type="graphic">objects/npcs/astersprite2.png</asset>
    <asset name="aster" type="graphic">objects/npcs/allaysprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="dersite1" type="graphic">objects/npcs/dersite1sprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="prospitan2" type="graphic">objects/npcs/prospitan2sprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="male" type="graphic">objects/npcs/malesprite.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='sisshop' walkableMap='sisshopMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='sisshopBG'>
	    <animation sheet='sisshopBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	  <sprite name="sisshopFG" depthing="2">
		<animation sheet="sisshopFG" />
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,411,627,465,589</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/houses.xml,houses,1065,714</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	</triggers>
	<sprite name='maleplace' x='362' y='542' width='30' height='60' collidable='true'>
	  <animation sheet='male' x='-20' y='-20'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
			@! They really do make a lot of these plushies, my kids love em but i don’t really see the appeal..

They all just sorta look the same to me,  tell me they make them based off random people they see but i just don’t buy it.

Like there’s no way we all look this identical, right?

		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='allayPlace' x='455' y='470' width='114' height='84' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='allay' x='-60' y='-50'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to Shop Clerk.'>
		<args>
			@vrachne_talk Vrachne: hey there.
			@aster_talk Aster: hey there lookin pretty fresh sister! what brings you to the good ole allay aster plushie parlor, i’m aster and she’s allay
@aster_talk Aster: hey allay say hi!
@allay_talk Allay: i’m trying to work back here but hello!
@aster_talk Aster: ahahaha nice
@aster_talk Aster: anyway, what’s the haps sister! Looking for something to buy or do you just wanna chat because i’m down for both 
@allay_flustured Allay: please stop talking to customers like that!
@aster_talk Aster: hey quit backseating my front desk work i told you i got this!
@allay_flustured Allay: fine but just try not to scare anyone off this time…
@aster_talk Aster: how many times do i have to tell you that was an accident!
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: you two sure have “fun” here don’t you?
@aster_talk Aster: hey if works fun then it ain’t really work is it!
@aster_talk Aster: anyway do you see anything ya like or maybe you want somethin custom made eh?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: well i’m not really in the market for toys right now.
@aster_talk Aster: well if you ask me a plush ain’t really that much of a toy unless you make it one
@aster_talk Aster: lots of people collect em!
@aster_talk Aster: mostly to just sell em later but that never really works out so they just keep em in an attic and occasionally give them away at a birthday party or something!
@allay_flustured Allay: ASTER!
@aster_talk Aster: hey i’m just being honest!
@aster_talk Aster: and honestly promotes good business!
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: well i don’t really have a cent to my name sorry 
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: maybe some other time
@aster_talk Aster: no worries! if you ever do get a cent to your name we’ll be here!
@aster_talk Aster: we’d love to make a plush outta you and your little friend!
@aster_talk Aster: it’d be a nice break from all the monochromancy we get around here
@aster_talk Aster: thats the word for it, right allay?
@allay_talk Allay: yes it is now could you please quiet down? i’m trying to focus
@aster_talk Aster: sorry boss!
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='asterPlace' x='750' y='490' width='30' height='102'>
          <animation sheet='aster' x='-10' y='-10'/>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='dersite1Place' x='576' y='430' width='30' height='92' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='dersite1' x='-10' y='-10'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Listen in.'>
		<args>
		@! #9900ff I love shopping in quaint little places like this, there’s really nothing else like it! ##

@! #ebb719 Yeah it’s pretty nice but you could totally get stuff like this in #674ea7 ONYX ## #ebb719 too ##

@! #9900ff No way! All the stuff over there has no soul you can totally tell it was made in like a factory or something! this stuff comes straight from the heart, you can tell from the stitching and the tags! ##

@! #ebb719 I mean there’s lots of nice local places in #674ea7 ONYX ## #ebb719 you just gotta know where to look. ##

@! #ebb719 You know i actually know a guy that does cybernetics stuff over there, he doesn’t need a permit to do it or anything! He just decided “hey i got nothing better to do, i worked with mechs and ships before, i’m gonna take that experience and try grafting that stuff into people” ##

@! #9900ff How’s that supposed to make me feel better about anything over there?! That’s horrifying! ##

@! #ebb719 What?! What’s so scary about a dude living his dre- ##

@! #9900ff The fact that he can just do that without getting a certificate or something first?! I mean seriously it’s one thing to be selling stuff without some license or something but that’s just taking it too far! ##

@! #ebb719 That’s just what it’s like over there man, everybody really just minds their own business unless you mess with em, ##

@! #ebb719 Nobody’s gonna be asking to see your “diploma” or whatever when they go to get a robot arm or something. ##

@! #ebb719 They’re gonna ask “hey how much is this gonna cost” and you’re gonna have to be the guy who strikes the right balance being too cheap or being so expensive that the only way you’d ever feasibly afford em would be to crash the stock market. ##

@! #ebb719 And lemme tell you, they learned how to make that thing crash proof. ##

@! #ebb719 I’m telling you someone over there running the place saw #cc0000 that one movie scene about the salamander stock crash ## #ebb719 and went “shit could that happen to us? We should do something about that”  ##

@! #9900ff Yeah i’m never going back to #674ea7 ONYX ##

@! #ebb719 Hey i ain’t gonna stop you but do you really have the cash to buy a house here? Heck i’m not even sure if you could buy a house here. ##

@! #ebb719 These guys don’t strike me as the type to have realtors or whatever ##

@! #9900ff ... ##

@! #ebb719 Cheer up bud, i’m telling you it isn’t that bad ##

@! #ebb719 Besides, anything’s better than the ## Battlefield, #ebb719 right? ##

@! #9900ff You got that right. ##
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='prospitan2Place' x='610' y='430' width='30' height='92' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='prospitan2' x='-10' y='-10'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Listen in.'>
		<args>
		@! #9900ff I love shopping in quaint little places like this, there’s really nothing else like it! ##

@! #ebb719 Yeah it’s pretty nice but you could totally get stuff like this in #674ea7 ONYX ## #ebb719 too ##

@! #9900ff No way! All the stuff over there has no soul you can totally tell it was made in like a factory or something! this stuff comes straight from the heart, you can tell from the stitching and the tags! ##

@! #ebb719 I mean there’s lots of nice local places in #674ea7 ONYX ## #ebb719 you just gotta know where to look. ##

@! #ebb719 You know i actually know a guy that does cybernetics stuff over there, he doesn’t need a permit to do it or anything! He just decided “hey i got nothing better to do, i worked with mechs and ships before, i’m gonna take that experience and try grafting that stuff into people” ##

@! #9900ff How’s that supposed to make me feel better about anything over there?! That’s horrifying! ##

@! #ebb719 What?! What’s so scary about a dude living his dre- ##

@! #9900ff The fact that he can just do that without getting a certificate or something first?! I mean seriously it’s one thing to be selling stuff without some license or something but that’s just taking it too far! ##

@! #ebb719 That’s just what it’s like over there man, everybody really just minds their own business unless you mess with em, ##

@! #ebb719 Nobody’s gonna be asking to see your “diploma” or whatever when they go to get a robot arm or something. ##

@! #ebb719 They’re gonna ask “hey how much is this gonna cost” and you’re gonna have to be the guy who strikes the right balance being too cheap or being so expensive that the only way you’d ever feasibly afford em would be to crash the stock market. ##

@! #ebb719 And lemme tell you, they learned how to make that thing crash proof. ##

@! #ebb719 I’m telling you someone over there running the place saw #cc0000 that one movie scene about the salamander stock crash ## #ebb719 and went “shit could that happen to us? We should do something about that”  ##

@! #9900ff Yeah i’m never going back to #674ea7 ONYX ##

@! #ebb719 Hey i ain’t gonna stop you but do you really have the cash to buy a house here? Heck i’m not even sure if you could buy a house here. ##

@! #ebb719 These guys don’t strike me as the type to have realtors or whatever ##

@! #9900ff ... ##

@! #ebb719 Cheer up bud, i’m telling you it isn’t that bad ##

@! #ebb719 Besides, anything’s better than the ## Battlefield, #ebb719 right? ##

@! #9900ff You got that right. ##
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>