<sburb description="stonerhouse">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="stonerhouseBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/stonerhouse.png</asset>
    <asset name="stonerhouseMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_interior/stonerhousecoll.png</asset>
    <asset name="langley" type="graphic">objects/npcs/langleysprite.png</asset>
    <asset name="waverly" type="graphic">objects/npcs/waverlysprite.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='stonerhouse' walkableMap='stonerhouseMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='stonerhouseBG'>
	    <animation sheet='stonerhouseBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,377,318,433,289</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/houses.xml,houses,935,909</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	</triggers>
	<sprite name='langleyPlace' x='600' y='310' width='40' height='90' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='langley' x='-20' y='-20'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: so im just going to assume little miss fuzzy there is your “acquaintance”
@langley_talk ???: that’s one word for it.
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: sucks to be you eh?
@langley_talk ???: god don’t even get me started
@langley_talk ???: she pulls stunts like this every goddamn day
@langley_talk ???: i honestly don’t know how much more of this i can take
@langley_talk ???: though it’s not like i can kick her out or anything like that because she owns the damn house
@langley_talk ???: “oh go room with somebody near the church Langley you’ll get lots of money and be successful”
@langley_talk Langley: last time i ever listen to my sisters advice, that arrogant ska-
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i don’t remember asking for your life story.
@langley_talk Langley: ugh
@langley_talk Langley: who even are you people? are you friends of hers?!
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: Do you really need to know.
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: I doubt we’ll be seeing each other again.
@langley_talk  Langley: whatever.
@langley_talk  Langley: You’re with that shaggy haired kid aren’t you?
@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: how’d ya figure that one out “brainiac” 
@langley_talk  Langley: He’s following around like his life depended on it so i just put two and two together
@langley_talk  Langley: You his mom or something?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: i guess you could say that
@langley_talk Langley: Well whatever you are, could you teach him not to barge into random peoples houses? Thanks.
@vranche_smug Vrachne: i’ll be sure to get rightttttt on that.
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	<sprite name='waverlyPlace' x='790' y='310' width='40' height='90' collidable='true'>
          <animation sheet='waverly' x='-20' y='-20'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
		@waverly_talk ???: Heyyyy welcome to the humble abodeeee
@waverly_talk ???: hows it hanginnnnn heh
@vrachne_confused Vrachne: fine i guess?
@waverly_talk ???: are you sure you’re all goodddddd whats goin on with your chesttt
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: excuse me?
@waverly_talk ???: do you got like cancer or somethin that sucksssssss
@waverly_talk ???: my grandma had that they had to like cut off her arms or something it was wildddddd
@waverly_talk ???: feel free to keep loookin arounddddd if you wanna keep your mind off it mannnnnn
@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: ….. (god this place SUCKSSSSSS)
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>