<sburb description="anticanonoutside">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="anticanonoutside" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/anticanon_map.png</asset>
    <asset name="anticanonMapOuter" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/anticanon_map_coll.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='anticanonoutside' walkableMap='anticanonMapOuter' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='anticanonoutside'>
	    <animation sheet='anticanonoutside'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,670,50,785,0</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/houses.xml,houses,1836,1917</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,671,641,778,521</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/anticanon.xml,anticanon,540,370</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	<trigger detonate='true'>
	  <args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 250</args>
	  <action command='talk'>
		<args>
		  @dickle_smug Dickle: i thought this alleyway seemed fishy!
@dickle_excited Dickle: look at that! It’s like a big staticy cracky thing.
@vrachne_concerned Vrachne: i don’t think this is supposed to be here
@vrachne_concerned Vrachne: actually i don’t think we’re supposed to be here either
@dickle_talk Dickle: well i coulda told you that
@dickle_talk Dickle: we literally walked through a fence!
@dickle_think Dickle: hmmm
@dickle_think Dickle: what do you think would happen if we touched this thing?
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Dickle.
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i thought the elevator thing was the stupidest thing you were gonna say today, but you’re just full of surprises
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: it’s honestly inspiring
@dickle_excited Dickle: you should learn to stop being so negative all the time!
@dickle_excited Dickle: seriously it’s just a bunch of static what’s the worst that could happen?
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i can think of a lot of things actually
@vrachne_shrug Vrachne: you could just explode, or maybe if you’re really unlucky you’d become some sort of deformed abomination, maybe with some spider pieces poking out of you, who knows
@dickle_smug Dickle: okay now you’re just being overdramatic 
@dickle_smug Dickle: i got a hunch absolutely none of those things will happen
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: and why’s that huh?
@dickle_explaining Dickle: well if someone exploded right here there probably would be a bunch of ya know… uh goop yeah spider goop and blood and stuff like that all over the place!
@dickle_explaining Dickle: people who worship abstract concepts like the sun probably aren’t known for keeping their hands to themselves if you know what i mean.
@vrachne_smug Vrachne: i don’t think you know what the word abstract means dickle.
@dickle_explaining Dickle: yeah but you probably don’t either. 
@dickle_happy Dickle: so that’s something we have in common! Hehehe
@dickle_excited Dickle: so come on, let’s just touch it and get this over with!
@vrachne_armup Vrachne: sure fine whatever, don’t listen to me. I’m sure this won’t backfire in anyway whatsoever 
@dickle_happy Dickle: hey if it does i’ll uh…. hmmm, oh yeah i got it! I’ll owe you a favor or something!
@dickle_airquotes Dickle: ya know an “anything goes” kinda favor!
@vrachne_smugcross Vrachne: deal!
@vrachne_smugcross Vrachne: but i don’t think you know what you’re getting yourself into by saying that dickle. 
@dickle_happy Dickle: well i guess we’ll cross that bridge when we come to it heh!
		</args>
	  </action>
	</trigger>
	</triggers>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>