<sburb description="booth">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="gateopen" type="graphic">objects/misc/gateopen_object.png</asset>
    <asset name="gateclosed" type="graphic">objects/misc/gate_object.png</asset>
    <asset name="boothBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map1.png</asset>
    <asset name="boothFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map1_fg.png</asset>
    <asset name="boothMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/map1coll.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='booth' walkableMap='boothMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name="boothFG" depthing="2">
        <animation sheet="boothFG" />
      </sprite>
	  <sprite name='boothBG'>
	    <animation sheet='boothBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	  <sprite name="gateclosed" x='865' y='806' width='330' height='352' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='gateclosed'/>
	  </sprite>
	  <sprite name="gateopen" x='865' y='806' width='330' height='352' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='gateopen'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
	<trigger detonate='true'>
          <args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 1240</args>
            <action command='talk' sprite='dickle'>
	    <args>
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: is this a tollbooth?
		@quincy_gruff ???: hey!!!
		@quincy_gruff ???: you two!
		@quincy_gruff ???: what’s your business here?!
		@dickle_smug Dickle: lemme handle this, i’ve got a real way with words
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: mhm whatever you say dickle.
		@vrachne_smugcross Vrachne: try not to embarrass yourself too bad.
		@dickle_smug Dickle: i’ll be fine!
		@quincy_gruff ???: HEY! 
		@quincy_gruff ???: is one of you gonna answer or what?!
		@dickle_talk Dickle: sorry sorry i was just talking to my friend here
		@dickle_talk Dickle: is this wallflower?
		@quincy_armscrossed ???: yeah it is, you can see the sign over there
		@quincy_armscrossed ???: you two tourists?
		@dickle_talk Dickle: i don’t think so, why?
		@quincy_armscrossed ???: we’ve gotten a lot of tourists round here recently
		@quincy_armscrossed ???: pitch black and pitch white you know
		@quincy_armscrossed ???: don’t know where they came from
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: ahhhh
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: me and my friend here aren’t tourists we’re looking for something related to the sun i think!
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: we met a nice guy who told us to come here, he went by da-niver i think
		@quincy_talk ???: that weirdo with the speech impediment?
		@dickle_talkcrossed Dickle: that’s not a very nice thing to say about him but yeah that guy!
		@quincy_talk ???: oh no don’t worry we’re good pals, he likes to riff on me for working at the gate so i like to riff on him by making fun of the silly way he talks
		@dickle_talk Dickle: ohhhhh you sound like good buds
		@quincy_talk???: ahahha yeah
		@quincy_friendly ???: well any friend of da-niver is a friend of mine!
		@quincy_friendly ???: i’m Quincy, nice to meet you folk!
		@dickle_happy Dickle: nice to meet you quincy
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: i’m Dickle and this is Vrachne!
		@vrachne_concerned(or something along those lines) Vrachne: ...
		@dickle_talk Dickle: she uhhh doesn’t talk much
		@dickle_talk Dickle: anyway, this is a beautiful town you got here! 
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: it sure is, guess that’s why we’re getting so many tourists now!
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: you two said you were looking for something sun related yeah?
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: yep we’ve got important business relating to it, i think.
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: you must be looking for the #f6b26b Church of Lindas ## then! it’s the best church on the planet!
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: Mostly because it’s the only one that’s actually still running heh!
		@dickle_excited Dickle: yeah that sounds like the place!
		@quincy_talk Quincy: it’s the big building up north you can’t miss it! 
		@quincy_talk Quincy: it’s run by some great people, i’m sure they’ll be able to help you out with whatever you need!
		@dickle_excited Dickle: gotcha! Thanks for all your help quincy!
		@quincy_talk Quincy: no problem! just promise me something okay?
		@quincy_talk Quincy: please don’t destroy anyone’s property 
		@quincy_talk Quincy: most of the tourist people have been pretty nice but some are just… lets just say they’re TOO MUCH
		@quincy_talk Quincy: if anything else gets broken i might be out of a job!
		@dickle_talk Dickle: we’ll be on our best behaviour i promise!
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: alright thats all i needed to hear
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: let me get that gate for you
	    </args>
	<action command='removeSprite'>
        	<args>secondRoomDoor,secondRoom</args>
	</action>
	  <sprite name="gateopen" x='865' y='806' width='330' height='352' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='gateopen'/>
	  </sprite>
		<args>
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: there you go!
		@quincy_friendly Quincy: hope you have a good time in town! Lindas be with you!
		@dickle_friendly Dickle: thanks man! Lindas be with you too
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: Whatever that means.
		</args>
	</action>
	</trigger>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,880,45,1140,0</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/square.xml,square,1008,2370</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	</triggers>
        </room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>
		