<sburb description="lift">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="liftBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/cave/lift_map.png</asset>
    <asset name="liftMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/cave/liftColl.png</asset>
    <asset name="lift_object" type="graphic">objects/misc/lift_object.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='lift' walkableMap='liftMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='liftBG'>
	    <animation sheet='liftBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<sprite name='lift_object' x='430' y='254' width='126' height='446' collidable='true'>
	  <animation sheet='lift_object' x='50' y='-50'/>
	  <action command='talk' name='Use lift.' sprite='dickle'>
	    <args>
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: oh nice wood
		@dickle_talk Dickle: just the thing i’d expect inside of a tree
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: obviously it’s some sort of lift dickle, look at the strings
		@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah you’re right, everything in here is pretty dim so i couldn’t really make anything out
		@dickle_talk Dickle: i guess you have better night vision than me eh?
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: it’s not even that dark in here dickle, maybe you should check those glasses of yours
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: i mean i’m gonna be honest these glasses are made more for looks than actually helping with vision at all
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: hell i think the longer i wear these things the worse my vision gets
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: why not just take them off 
		@dickle_talk Dickle: no way! I’d look like a jackass without them
		@dickle_talk Dickle: they make my entire face!
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: they really can’t make that much of a difference
		@dickle_talk Dickle: you’d be surprised! I’ve looked at myself in the mirror before without them and it’s NOT PRETTY
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: prove it then! Take em off
		@dickle_talk Dickle: alright fine but don’t say i didn’t warn you!
		@dickle_horror Dickle:  BAM
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: i’ve seen worse.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: yeah you probably have, but plenty of other people haven’t!
		@dickle_talk Dickle: so i’ll keep them on
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: whatever.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: i swear fashion over function will be the death of me, heh
		@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah speaking of dying
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: do you think this whole lift thing is safe?
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: this thing looks pretty rickety ya know
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: it’ll be fine dickle, if this leads somewhere then someone has to have used it before right?
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: it would’ve crashed on them if it was so “rickety”
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: but what if it can’t handle our weight or something like that!
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Dickle. I’ll give you a solid 6 seconds to figure out why that is the single stupidest thing i’ve heard you say so far
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: 6… 5… 4… 3… 2… 1…
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: time's up. do you have an answer?
		<action command='presentAction'>
		  <args>
			<action command='talk' name='Answer.'>
			  <args>
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: it’s because you can float right, sorry….
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: that’s it, good job
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: there’s hope for you yet
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: i might be a bit slow sometimes but i do my best to listen to other people! it’s just common courtesy
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: i’ll keep that in mind
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: but like, If this thing does fall for whatever reason 
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: you’ll catch me right?
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: yes?! of course i would, i’m not a psychopath
				@dickle_happy Dickle: Danke! thats uh german for thanks!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Honestly i’m pretty hurt that you’d assume i’m that “heartless”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: and you don’t need to thank me this time dickle, it’s my “job”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Letting you die would be a pretty huge failure on my part, so of course i wouldn’t let that happen
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: well, if i have someone like you looking out for me i might as well be invincible!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i’m not your crutch dickle.
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah of course, i won’t be relying on you for everything 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: i’ll be doing my best to get better too
				@dickle_excited Dickle: heck if i can get a grip like yours, nobody would mess with me!
				@vrachne_smug Vrachne: you can have the strongest grip imaginable but it won’t matter if you can’t even get close to someone.
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: but we’ll save fighting talk for later, we should really get on with this don’t you think?
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh right! 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: got sidetracked again
				<action command="changeRoom">
					<args>booth,1010,2400</args>
	  			</action>
			  </args>
			</action>
			<action command='talk' name="Don't Answer.">
			  <args>
				@vrachne_horror Vrachne: IT’S BECAUSE I CAN FLOAT DICKLE
				@vrachne_horror Vrachne: HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU I CAN FLOAT
				@dickle_angryflustered Dickle: SORRY!!!!!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: you’re so lucky to have someone like me around dickle
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: you’d be pretty hopeless otherwise
				@dickle_flustered Dickle: hey i can hold my own! I’m just a bit slow sometimes..
				@vrachne_shrug Vrachne: whatever you say dickle
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: but like, If this thing does fall for whatever reason 
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: you’ll catch me right?
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: yes?! of course i would, i’m not a psychopath
				@dickle_happy Dickle: Danke! thats uh german for thanks!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Honestly i’m pretty hurt that you’d assume i’m that “heartless”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: and you don’t need to thank me this time dickle, it’s my “job”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Letting you die would be a pretty huge failure on my part, so of course i wouldn’t let that happen
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: well, if i have someone like you looking out for me i might as well be invincible!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i’m not your crutch dickle.
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah of course, i won’t be relying on you for everything 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: i’ll be doing my best to get better too
				@dickle_excited Dickle: heck if i can get a grip like yours, nobody would mess with me!
				@vrachne_smug Vrachne: you can have the strongest grip imaginable but it won’t matter if you can’t even get close to someone.
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: but we’ll save fighting talk for later, we should really get on with this don’t you think?
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh right! 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: got sidetracked again
				<action command="changeRoom">
					<args>booth,1010,2400</args>
	  			</action>
			  </args>
			</action>
		  </args>
		</action>
	    </args>
	  </action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>