<sburb description="lift">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="liftBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/cave/lift_map.png</asset>
    <asset name="liftMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/cave/liftColl.png</asset>
    <asset name="lift_object" type="graphic">objects/misc/lift_object.png</asset>
    <asset name="cutscene" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_cutscene.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='lift' walkableMap='liftMap' mapScale="1">
	  <sprite name='liftBG'>
	    <animation sheet='liftBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<sprite name='lift_object' x='620' y='400' width='126' height='446' collidable='true'>
	  <animation sheet='lift_object' x='-100' y='-200'/>
	  <action command='talk' name='Use lift.'>
	    <args>
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: oh nice wood
		@dickle_talk Dickle: just the thing i’d expect inside of a tree
		@vrachne_armup Vrachne: obviously it’s some sort of lift dickle, look at the strings
		@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah you’re right, everything in here is pretty dim so i couldn’t really make anything out
		@dickle_talk Dickle: i guess you have better night vision than me eh?
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: it’s not even that dark in here dickle, maybe you should check those glasses of yours
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: i mean i’m gonna be honest these glasses are made more for looks than actually helping with vision at all
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: hell i think the longer i wear these things the worse my vision gets
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: why not just take them off 
		@dickle_talk Dickle: no way! I’d look like a jackass without them
		@dickle_talk Dickle: they make my entire face!
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: they really can’t make that much of a difference
		@dickle_talk Dickle: you’d be surprised! I’ve looked at myself in the mirror before without them and it’s NOT PRETTY
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: prove it then! Take em off
		@dickle_talk Dickle: alright fine but don’t say i didn’t warn you!
		@dickle_horror Dickle:  BAM
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: i’ve seen worse.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: yeah you probably have, but plenty of other people haven’t!
		@dickle_talk Dickle: so i’ll keep them on
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: whatever.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: i swear fashion over function will be the death of me, heh
		@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah speaking of dying
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: do you think this whole lift thing is safe?
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: this thing looks pretty rickety ya know
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: it’ll be fine dickle, if this leads somewhere then someone has to have used it before right?
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: it would’ve crashed on them if it was so “rickety”
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: but what if it can’t handle our weight or something like that!
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Dickle. I’ll give you a solid 6 seconds to figure out why that is the single stupidest thing i’ve heard you say so far
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: 6… 5… 4… 3… 2… 1…
		@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: time's up. do you have an answer?
	    </args>
		<action command='presentAction'>
		  <args>
			<action command='talk' name='Answer.'>
			  <args>
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: it’s because you can float right, sorry….
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: that’s it, good job
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: there’s hope for you yet
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: i might be a bit slow sometimes but i do my best to listen to other people! it’s just common courtesy
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: i’ll keep that in mind
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: but like, If this thing does fall for whatever reason 
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: you’ll catch me right?
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: yes?! of course i would, i’m not a psychopath
				@dickle_happy Dickle: Danke! thats uh german for thanks!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Honestly i’m pretty hurt that you’d assume i’m that “heartless”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: and you don’t need to thank me this time dickle, it’s my “job”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Letting you die would be a pretty huge failure on my part, so of course i wouldn’t let that happen
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: well, if i have someone like you looking out for me i might as well be invincible!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i’m not your crutch dickle.
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah of course, i won’t be relying on you for everything 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: i’ll be doing my best to get better too
				@dickle_excited Dickle: heck if i can get a grip like yours, nobody would mess with me!
				@vrachne_smug Vrachne: you can have the strongest grip imaginable but it won’t matter if you can’t even get close to someone.
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: but we’ll save fighting talk for later, we should really get on with this don’t you think?
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh right! 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: got sidetracked again
				@! With a loud CLUNK the lever shifts into place and the elevator begins descending “swiftly” if your definition of swiftly is being a slow rickety piece of shit, you almost consider filing a complaint to the consort equivalent of OSHA before realizing that, One, that would be an incredibly silly thing to do, and two, You can’t write for shit.

@! As you descend you begin to consider what actually awaits at the bottom of all this, with all the walking it took you to get here you hope at the very least they have a convenience store or something, maybe even a hotel!

It’d be nice to lay down, get some rest and maybe ev--
			  </args>
				<sprite name='cutscene' x='520' y='400' depthing='3'>
				<animation sheet='cutscene'/>
				</sprite>
			<action command='talk'>
			<args>@! Before you can finish your thoughts your eyes bear witness to something you weren’t at all expecting.

A sprawling city and a dazzling display of lights as far as your eyes can see, though considering the fact that you have to wear glasses to see 5 feet in front of you at any given moment, it’s probably less impressive than it sounds.


Whatever the case you attempt to think of something to say to make the ride down less quiet but.. It’s nice to have moments of calm like this,  a sentiment your “partner” seems to share.

@! It gives you time to think about other things, like the question of how they’d manage to build all this, you know in your heart that it’s all just game generated fancy scenery but it’s fun to try to give it all context.

But an entire city underground just seems a bit ridiculous to put it politely.

The logistics of it all is almost too much to think about, questions begin to surge like “how do they get power” and the only answer you can think of is water? you didn’t see any coming in but it could be there you guess?

and where the hell is the light in this place even coming from?! you know they probably have lamps and stuff but that wouldn’t light this entire cavern would it?

@! If you had to guess you’d probably say “oh the big church with the obnoxious sun on it is probably doing that” but that just seems so obvious, but then again something being obvious has never stopped it from being true has it?

Eventually after you realize that all of your questions are ultimately pointless and don’t really matter that much in the grand scheme of things you finally arrive at the bottom of what could loosely be called an “elevator shaft” and exit the lift.

It’s then you realize that once again, you have more walking to do. How fun.
			</args>
			<action command="changeRoom">
		<args>booth,1010,2400</args>
	  	</action>
		</action>
			</action>
			<action command='talk' name="Don't Answer.">
			  <args>
				@vrachne_horror Vrachne: IT’S BECAUSE I CAN FLOAT DICKLE
				@vrachne_horror Vrachne: HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU I CAN FLOAT
				@dickle_angryflustered Dickle: SORRY!!!!!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: you’re so lucky to have someone like me around dickle
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: you’d be pretty hopeless otherwise
				@dickle_flustered Dickle: hey i can hold my own! I’m just a bit slow sometimes..
				@vrachne_shrug Vrachne: whatever you say dickle
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: but like, If this thing does fall for whatever reason 
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: you’ll catch me right?
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: yes?! of course i would, i’m not a psychopath
				@dickle_happy Dickle: Danke! thats uh german for thanks!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Honestly i’m pretty hurt that you’d assume i’m that “heartless”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: and you don’t need to thank me this time dickle, it’s my “job”
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Letting you die would be a pretty huge failure on my part, so of course i wouldn’t let that happen
				@dickle_explaining Dickle: well, if i have someone like you looking out for me i might as well be invincible!
				@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: i’m not your crutch dickle.
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh yeah of course, i won’t be relying on you for everything 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: i’ll be doing my best to get better too
				@dickle_excited Dickle: heck if i can get a grip like yours, nobody would mess with me!
				@vrachne_smug Vrachne: you can have the strongest grip imaginable but it won’t matter if you can’t even get close to someone.
				@vrachne_talk Vrachne: but we’ll save fighting talk for later, we should really get on with this don’t you think?
				@dickle_talk Dickle: oh right! 
				@dickle_talk Dickle: got sidetracked again
				@! With a loud CLUNK the lever shifts into place and the elevator begins descending “swiftly” if your definition of swiftly is being a slow rickety piece of shit, you almost consider filing a complaint to the consort equivalent of OSHA before realizing that, One, that would be an incredibly silly thing to do, and two, You can’t write for shit.

@! As you descend you begin to consider what actually awaits at the bottom of all this, with all the walking it took you to get here you hope at the very least they have a convenience store or something, maybe even a hotel!

It’d be nice to lay down, get some rest and maybe ev--
			  </args>
		<sprite name='cutscene' x='520' y='400' depthing='3'>
				<animation sheet='cutscene'/>
				</sprite>
			<action command='talk'>
			<args>@! Before you can finish your thoughts your eyes bear witness to something you weren’t at all expecting.

A sprawling city and a dazzling display of lights as far as your eyes can see, though considering the fact that you have to wear glasses to see 5 feet in front of you at any given moment, it’s probably less impressive than it sounds.


Whatever the case you attempt to think of something to say to make the ride down less quiet but.. It’s nice to have moments of calm like this,  a sentiment your “partner” seems to share.

@! It gives you time to think about other things, like the question of how they’d manage to build all this, you know in your heart that it’s all just game generated fancy scenery but it’s fun to try to give it all context.

But an entire city underground just seems a bit ridiculous to put it politely.

The logistics of it all is almost too much to think about, questions begin to surge like “how do they get power” and the only answer you can think of is water? you didn’t see any coming in but it could be there you guess?

and where the hell is the light in this place even coming from?! you know they probably have lamps and stuff but that wouldn’t light this entire cavern would it?

@! If you had to guess you’d probably say “oh the big church with the obnoxious sun on it is probably doing that” but that just seems so obvious, but then again something being obvious has never stopped it from being true has it?

Eventually after you realize that all of your questions are ultimately pointless and don’t really matter that much in the grand scheme of things you finally arrive at the bottom of what could loosely be called an “elevator shaft” and exit the lift.

It’s then you realize that once again, you have more walking to do. How fun.
			</args>
			<action command="changeRoom">
		<args>booth,1010,2400</args>
	  	</action>
		</action>
			</action>
	    </args>
	  </action>
	</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>