<sburb description="shop">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="shopBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map3.png</asset>
    <asset name="shopMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/map3coll.png</asset>
    <asset name="shopFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/wallflower_exterior/wallflower_map3_fg.png</asset>
    <asset name="log" type="graphic">objects/npcs/logsprite.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
	<room name='shop' walkableMap='shopMap' mapScale="1">
	<sprite name="shopFG" depthing="2">
        <animation sheet="shopFG" />
      </sprite>
	  <sprite name='shopBG'>
	    <animation sheet='shopBG'/>
	  </sprite>
	<triggers>
		<trigger>
  			<args>inBox2,char,2370,1130,2410,870</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/square.xml,square,150,900</args>
			</action>
  		</trigger>
		<trigger>
			<args>inBox2,char,985,837,1043,786</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/giftshop.xml,giftshop,431,475</args>
			</action>
		</trigger>
	</triggers>
	<sprite name='log' x='1742' y='867' width='30' height='48' collidable='true'>
		<animation sheet='log' x='0' y='0'/>
		<action command='talk' name='Talk to spider.'>
		<args>
			@dickle_talk Dickle: oh dang crispy looking house you got here is it alright if i asked what happened to it?
@log_talk ???: Same story as all the other fires recently, someone pushed their lights too hard and  then poof! up in smoke.
@log_talk ???: Perhaps we were never meant to hold the power of the sun in such small glass prisons….
@log_talk ???: hey wait a second you’re not from around here are you!? are you another tourist?
@dickle_talkcrossed Dickle: uh no i’m just here on business i guess
@dickle_talk Dickle: lots of talk in this town about tourists and stuff though do you get a lot of them around here?
@log_talk ???: until recently this place was pretty quiet but nowadays you can’t even go a day without some rowdy rockers causing a scene! heck that’s the reason the pub is closed.
@log_talk ???: real shame too, you never really know how much you’d miss happy hour until it’s gone.
@dickle_talk Dickle: oof that sounds pretty rough, got any idea what caused the uptick in tourism? I’m curious
@log_talk ???: they keep talking about some “war being called off” or something like that it’s wild stuff
@log_talk ???: i’ve never heard about any wars! outside of like the old history stories and stuff
@log_talk ???: but then again i’ve never really stepped foot out of town before so what do i know!
@dickle_talk Dickle: the worlds a big place it’s crazy!
@dickle_talk Dickle: hey do you mind if i ask you what your name is?
@log_talk ???: only if you tell me yours first, that’s common courtesy!
@dickle_happy Dickle: oh of course! I’m Dickle nice to meet cha
@log_talk ???: I’m Logly but people just call me Log for short
@log_talk Log: i make sure the buildings around here are up to snuff so to speak, if you want your buildings well kept i’m your guy!
@dickle_talk Dickle: well i’ll give you if my house ever starts creaking heh
@dickle_excited Dickle: it was nice talking to you man!  hope for your sake that things stop catching on fire.
@log_talk Log: you and me both!
		</args>
		</action>
	</sprite>
	</room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>