<sburb description="tree">
  <dependencies>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="treeFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/foreground.png</asset>
    <asset name="treeBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/background.png</asset>
    <asset name="treeMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/collision-map.png</asset>
    <asset name="moveTrigger" type="graphic">objects/misc/movetrigger.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
    <room name="tree" walkableMap="treeMap" mapScale="1">
      <sprite name="treeFG" depthing="2">
        <animation sheet="treeFG" />
      </sprite>
      <sprite name="treeBG">
        <animation sheet="treeBG" />
      </sprite>
    <triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,300,1250,450,1200</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/forest.xml,forest,2125,900</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	<trigger detonate='true'>
        	<args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 650</args>
			<action command="changeRoom">
				<args>cave,1015,2494</args>
			</action>
	</trigger>
      <trigger detonate='true'>
        <args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 800</args>
        <action sprite='dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: oh god is this it
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: judging by the fact that it’s a big tree, i’d say yes.
		@dickle_excited Dickle: oh thank GOD FINALLY
		@dickle_talk Dickle: this thing sure looks different up close eh vrachne?
		@vrachne_explaining Vrachne: distance is a hell of a thing, the glasses probably didn’t help that much either.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: you got that right
		@dickle_smug Dickle: thing looks like a modern art sculpture hehehehe
		@dickle_smug Dickle: whole lot of nothing around here though, are you sure this is the place we’re looking for?
		@vrachne_armup Vrachne: trees don’t just grow like this dickle, someone or something must’ve made it like this.
		@vrachne_armup Vrachne: maybe you should try actually looking around before declaring there’s “nothing” here.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: alright alright fine let’s look around then
	  </args>
	</action>
	<action sprite='!dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: this is it, we’re here.
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: took us long enough.
		@dickle_excited Dickle: woooooo finally!
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: uhhhhh….
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: hey are you sure this is the place vrachne? there seems to be a whole lot of nothing aside from the big modern art sculpture
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: Dickle. it’s a giant tree with webs on it, in the middle of its own little important looking pond in an open clearing.
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: this is the most obvious environmental sign posting i’ve ever seen.
		@vrachne_amrup Vrachne: there’s gonna be something around here that’ll lead us where we need to go, probably a switch or maybe a hole who knows.
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: let’s look around.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: alright lead the way!
	  </args>
	</action>
      </trigger>
      <trigger detonate='true'>
	<args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 675</args>
	<action sprite='dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@dickle_happy Dickle: oh hey wait there’s a hole here vrachne!
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: i’m right behind you dickle you don’t need to yell
		@dickle_talk Dickle: right, sorry.
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: told you there was something here.
		@dickle_flustered Dickle: yeah yeah you don’t have to rub it in.
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: oh i know, but i like doing it anyway.
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: it helps people learn important lessons!
		@vrachne_smugshrug Vrachne: lessons like “how to actually use your eyes to see very obvious things”
		@vrachne_smugcrossed Vrachne: which is a pretty niche lesson i do admit, but obviously it’s helped you out (::.
		@dickle_angryflustered Dickle: Verpiss Dich! my glasses are all foggy, i’m tired and the tree is all one color! It all blended together!
		@dickle_angryflustered Dickle: can we just get in this hole already?!
		@vrachne_chuckle Vrachne: ahueahueahueahue 
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: you really do have a way with words dickle
		@vrachne_smugairquotes Vrachne: but sure, i’d love to “explore” a hole with you.
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: we might not like what we find in it.
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: i learned that the hard way.
		@vrachne_smugcross Vrachne: what’d you find in the last “weird hole” that you explored dickle? 
		@dickle_talk Dickle: sword with porn on it.
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: you’re joking.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: no really! It was my dad’s old porn sword actually
		@dickle_explaining Dickle: it was really bad porn and i used it to make my sword that has slightly more acceptable porn on it!
		@vrachne_laugh Vrachne: AHUEAHUEAHUEAHUEAHUE
		@vrachne_laugh Vrachne: gosh your family sounds like an absolute “riot” dickle.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: tell me about it! thankfully i don’t have a sister
		@dickle_talk Dickle: shudder to think about what she’d put on a sword
		@dickle_talk Dickle: anyway enough about me and my weird family
		@dickle_talk Dickle: it’s time for cave explore!
		@vrachne_smugcross Vrachne: you first, dickle.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: wouldn’t have it any other way
	    </args>
	  </action>
	<action sprite='!dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@dickle_sad Dickle: ugh my socks are all wet now...
		@dickle_sad Dickle: thank god im wearing shorts.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: hey have you found anything yet?
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: found it.
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: see? i told you there was more to this place!
		@dickle_happy Dickle: oh niceeee 
		@dickle_excited Dickle: it’s a hole!
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: wait can we actually even fit in there?
		@vrachne_armup Vrachne: i’d say it’s about the size of an overgrown spider that’s gotten the bright idea to stand on two of its legs so yes, might be a bit of a squeeze though
		@dickle_fingerguns Dickle: alright let’s go, ladies first though eh?
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: how courteous. 
	    </args>
	  </action>
	</trigger>
    </triggers>
	<sprite name='moveTrigger'> x='350' y='625' width='50' height='50'>
          <action command='talk' name='Enter.'>
		<args>
			<action command="changeRoom">
          		<args>cave,1015,2494</args>
			</action>
		</args>
       	 </action>
	</sprite>
    </room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>