<sburb description="tree">
  <dependencies>
	<dependency>rooms/forest.xml</dependency>
  </dependencies>
  <assets>
    <asset name="treeFG" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/foreground.png</asset>
    <asset name="treeBG" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/background.png</asset>
    <asset name="treeMap" type="graphic">backgrounds/tree/collision-map.png</asset>
    <asset name="moveTrigger" type="graphic">objects/misc/movetrigger.png</asset>
  </assets>
  <rooms>
    <room name="tree" walkableMap="treeMap" mapScale="1">
      <sprite name="treeFG" depthing="2">
        <animation sheet="treeFG" />
      </sprite>
      <sprite name="treeBG">
        <animation sheet="treeBG" />
      </sprite>
    <triggers>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,300,1250,450,1200</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/forest.xml,forest,2125,1000</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
	<trigger>
  		<args>inBox2,char,300,650,450,600</args>
  			<action command='changeRoomRemote'>
         			 <args>rooms/cave.xml,cave,1015,2475</args>
			</action>
  	</trigger>
      <trigger detonate='true'>
        <args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 800</args>
        <action sprite='dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: this is it we’re here
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: took us long enough
@dickle_excited Dickle: woooooo finally!
@dickle_talk Dickle: uhhhhh….
@dickle_think Dickle: hey are you sure this is the place vrachne? there seems to be a whole lot of nothing aside from the big modern art sculpture
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: Dickle. it’s a giant tree with webs on it, in the middle of its own little important looking pond in an open clearing.
@vrachne_peevedcross Vrachne: this is the most obvious environmental sign posting i’ve ever seen.
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: there’s gonna be something around here that’ll lead us where we need to go, probably a switch or maybe a hole who knows.
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: let’s look around.
@dickle_talk Dickle: alright lead the way! 
	  </args>
	</action>
	<action sprite='!dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: this is it, we’re here.
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: took us long enough.
		@dickle_excited Dickle: woooooo finally!
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: uhhhhh….
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: hey are you sure this is the place vrachne? there seems to be a whole lot of nothing aside from the big modern art sculpture
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: Dickle. it’s a giant tree with webs on it, in the middle of its own little important looking pond in an open clearing.
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: this is the most obvious environmental sign posting i’ve ever seen.
		@vrachne_amrup Vrachne: there’s gonna be something around here that’ll lead us where we need to go, probably a switch or maybe a hole who knows.
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: let’s look around.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: alright lead the way!
	  </args>
	</action>
      </trigger>
      <trigger detonate='true'>
	<args>spriteProperty,char,y &lt; 675</args>
	<action sprite='dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: ugh my socks are all wet now..
@dickle_glasses Dickle: thank god im wearing shorts.
@dickle_smug Dickle: hey have you found anything yet?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: found it
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: see? i told you there was more to this place!
@dickle_excited Dickle: oh niceeee 
@dickle_excited Dickle: it’s a hole!
@dickle_think Dickle: wait can we actually even fit in there?
@vrachne_talk Vrachne: i’d say it’s about the size of an overgrown spider that’s gotten the bright idea to stand on two of its legs so yes, might be a bit of a squeeze though
@dickle_fingerguns Dickle: alright let’s go, ladies first though eh?
@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: how courteous. 
	    </args>
	  </action>
	<action sprite='!dickle' command='talk'>
	  <args>
		@dickle_sad Dickle: ugh my socks are all wet now...
		@dickle_sad Dickle: thank god im wearing shorts.
		@dickle_talk Dickle: hey have you found anything yet?
		@vrachne_talk Vrachne: found it.
		@vrachne_smug Vrachne: see? i told you there was more to this place!
		@dickle_happy Dickle: oh niceeee 
		@dickle_excited Dickle: it’s a hole!
		@dickle_glasses Dickle: wait can we actually even fit in there?
		@vrachne_armup Vrachne: i’d say it’s about the size of an overgrown spider that’s gotten the bright idea to stand on two of its legs so yes, might be a bit of a squeeze though
		@dickle_fingerguns Dickle: alright let’s go, ladies first though eh?
		@vrachne_peeved Vrachne: how courteous. 
	    </args>
	  </action>
	</trigger>
    </triggers>
	<sprite name='moveTrigger'> x='350' y='625' width='50' height='50'>
          <action command='talk' name='Enter.'>
		<args>
			<action command="changeRoom">
          		<args>cave,1015,2494</args>
			</action>
		</args>
       	 </action>
	</sprite>
    </room>
  </rooms>
</sburb>